archiveorange.com 2012-12-06

# Privacy Policy - ArchiveOrange

### Archive Counter

  * Archiving 3,856 active mailing lists, 8,832 total
  * Received 16,954 messages yesterday
  * Last time I counted, there were about 50,276,295 messages in the archive.

Search Archived Messages

## Summay

ArchiveOrange.com does not utilize cookies for visitor tracking, but third-party partners such as Google Adsense do. Under no circumstances is personal information contained in e-mail messages disclosed to any third party.

## The Fine Print

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [orange@archiveorange.com](mailto:orange@archiveorange.com).

##### Log Files

ArchiveOrange.com makes use of standard server log files. The information collected in these include IP addresses, browser user agents, date/time stamps, and referring pages. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

##### Cookies and Web Beacons

ArchiveOrange.com does not use cookies.

##### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ArchiveOrange.com.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ArchiveOrange.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ArchiveOrange.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ArchiveOrange.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ArchiveOrange.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
